Alright, the next part of this section, I'm actually going to go over the TypeScript edition of this.
好的，本节的下一部分，我就真的要向你展示这个的 TypeScript 版本了
But for all intents and purposes, you've successfully created your first Hardhead project,
但不管怎么讲，你都已经成功创建了你的第一个 Hardhat 项目了
you've done a ton of amazing things. In this lesson,
你已经在这节课中完成了许多了不起的事情了
let's do a quick refresher of what we've learned so far,
现在让我们快速回顾一下目前为止我们学到的内容
we learned how to spin up our own hard hat projects.
我们学习了如何启动我们的 Hardhat 项目
And now we can run yarn, hard hat
现在我们可以运行 "yarn hardhat"
and see a list of the tasks and different things that we can do with hard hat.
并查看可以使用 Hardhat 执行的任务和其他操作的列表
We learned that hard hat looks for this hard hat.config.js.
我们了解了 Hardhat 会寻找这个 "hardhat.config.js"
And this is sort of the entry point for any task that we run that starts with hard hat,
这是我们运行任何以 "hardhat" 开头的任务的入口
we learned we can add our contracts to this contracts folder.
我们学习了可以添加我们的合约到这个 "contracts" 文件夹
And then we compile it by running yarn, art half compile,
然后可以执行 "yarn hardhat compile" 来编译它
we learned that all the compliation goes into the artifacts and then the cache as well.
我们学习了所有的编译结果都会存放在 "artifacts" 和 "cache" 中
And if we want to clean reset, we can either delete these two files
并且如果我们想清空和重置，那么可以删除这两个文件
or just run yarn, hard hat clean.
或是执行 "yarn hardhat clean"
So we learned that we can use scripts or tasks
我们还学习了如何使用脚本和任务
to actually deploy, interact and do things with our smart contracts.
来部署，交互和处理我们的智能合约
We also learned that I'm going to be using scripts for the rest of this course.
我们还学到了在这个课程的剩余部分我都将使用脚本
But if you want, you could absolutely use tasks as well.
但如果你想的话，也完全可以使用任务
I've asked this question a million times what's the difference?
我已经问过了无数次这二者有什么区别
Nobody really seems to know what the main difference is.
但似乎没有人真正知道它们的主要区别是什么
But I think the main difference is that tasks are for plugins.
不过我认为主要区别是任务用于插件
And scripts are for your local development Mart, that is mind limiter,
而脚本用于你的本地开发模式，这是我的看法
we learned that we can import a whole bunch of things,
我们还学习了可以导入这么一大堆东西到我们的脚本中
including tasks from hard hat in our scripts,
其中就包括 Hardhat 的任务
and we can work with our async functions to grab our contracts and deploy them,
并且我们可以使用异步函数来获取我们的合约并部署它们
we actually then can programmatically verify them using hard hat and using hard hat plugins.
我们还可以使用 Hardhat 和 Hardhat 的插件来程序化地验证它们
And then additionally, we can interact with our contracts very similar to how we did it with ethers.
此外我们还可以使用与 ethers 非常相似的方法与合约进行交互
We wrote a wonderful verification script.
我们编写了一个非常棒的验证脚本
And we also wrote our own task,
还编写了一个我们自己的任务
we wrote our first test for this whole space.
我们为整个空间编写了第一个测试
And we showed what our tests are going to look like moving forward.
并展示了我们未来的测试形式
And we talked a little bit about their importance.
我们还稍微谈了点测试的重要性
And I really should stress that
并且我十分强调
writing good tests is going to be the difference between a really professional environment and kind of a side project.
是否编写了一个好的测试是一个项目专业还是业余的主要区别
Whenever I audit smart contracts,
每当我审计智能合约时
or whenever I'm given a project for someone to tell me to take a look at.
或是每当有人给我一个项目让我去瞧一瞧的时候
The first thing I look at is the readme, of course.
我的第一件事是阅读 README，这是当然的了
And the second thing I look at is the tests.
而第二件事就是查看它的测试
And if tests aren't good, I usually tell them,
如果测试写的不好，我就会告诉他们
hey, you need to go back to the drawing board, and you need to level up your tests.
嘿，你得重头开始，并且提升一下你的测试水平
So tests are really really important, especially for this space,
因此测试非常非常的重要，尤其是对这个领域来说
we learned about a couple of more environment variables we
can use. We learned about a couple of tools to see how good
our tests are one of them being coverage. We also learn about a
gas reporter to see how much it's going to cost us when we
actually deploy to a real network. We learned a ton about
the hard hat config, and how there are multiple networks that
we can add add to our hard heads, we can make our project
our EVM code, work with any network out there, we started
working with dev dependencies instead of regular dependencies.
Now, READMEs are something that I'm not really going to go over
too deeply in here. But READMEs are sort of like the welcome
page of your GitHub repository, and really should give you an
understanding of what your code does. Being a part of the web
through space. And being a part of the blockchain ecosystem is
really more than just you coding your stuff by yourself. You want
other people to interact and engage with your code and engage
with your projects. I haven't showed you how to use GitHub
yet. But don't worry, we're going to but if you look at my
heart had simple storage readme. If you scroll down, usually, you
really want to have a Getting Started section where you define
how to set up all the code and how to set everything up a
Quickstart section, and maybe a usage section and some testing
section, which teaches people how to actually use and interact
with your code. Since we're just learning more of the code part
and not so much the readme part. For now, we're not going to go
over how to make a fantastic readme. However, I will leave a
link in the GitHub repository associated with this course,
link to this best readme template. It really is a
fantastic readme template that you can copy to any of your
projects to make them look really good and give them a
really good setup, so that other developers can come to your
project, and learn and participate with what you're
coding. But all right, you have learned an absolute ton, you
should be incredibly proud of yourself, and incredibly excited
that you've made it this far. Now I'm going to jump into the
TypeScript section here. So for those of you who are coding
along with TypeScript, feel free to follow along. For those of
you who are not, you just finished the Basic section on
hard hit, but stick around the next to heart out sections are
going to be the ones that really fine grain and hone your skills,
and give you all the fundamentals for working with
these frameworks. So be sure to follow along with the next two
sections, we've got a ton more fantastic content for you, we
are just beginning to get deeper into the smart contract
ecosystem. So take that lap, get that coffee, and I'll see you
soon.